Kasane!
카사네
Kasane! Kasane!
카사네...
Where are we?
여기는...
Kasane, look at that.
카사네, 저쪽 봐봐
That's the Kunad Highway.
여기는 쿠나도 고속도로잖아
What happened?
무슨 일이 있었던 거야?
We have no idea.
우리도 잘 몰라
This was what we woke up to.
깨어보니 이렇게 되었더라고
What is going on here?
대체 어떻게 된 거야?
All I can remember was the earthquake.
지진이 일어났던 것밖에 기억 안 나
Was that thing caused by an earthquake?
지진 때문에 저렇게 된 거라고?
We wouldn't know.
모르지
Gravity around that thing is abnormal.
저 주위에만 중력이 이상 반응을 일으켰으니까
We can't contact Haruka.
하루카도 연락 안 되고
Luka and Yuito are nowhere to be seen.
루카와 유이토도 안 보여
Even Yuito too?
유이토마저...
This can't be happening.
어떻게 이런 일이
Damn it! How did this happen?
젠장, 이게 다 뭐야
Calm down, Shiden.
진정해, 시덴
If Karen really betrays us all,
카렌이 진짜 반란을 일으킨 거라면
something might unfold in Suoh.
스오에도 변화가 있겠지
Yes. Let's return to Suoh.
맞아, 스오에 돌아가자
What happened here?
대체 무슨 일이 일어난 걸까?
SCARLET NEXUS
"스칼렛넥서"
♫A crime in reality♫
현실의 Crimｅ
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven`s sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
거짓을 받아들여
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
영원한 환상은 점점 사라져가
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
결코 완벽하지 않아 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
뒤돌아 걸어오는 소녀는
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
순간 이 세상에 기적을 남겨
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
최고의 게임을 찾았어
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I`ve never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
난 언제부터 이런 세상이 질렸던 걸까
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won`t be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
더는 해치고 싶지 않기에 나를 희생해
A TOMORROW OF RUIN
(파멸된 내일)
Is this Suoh?
여기... 스오 맞지?
What happened to it?
이게 다 뭐야?
The whole city is non-operational.
시티 기능 전멸이라
Is Arahabaki still in operation?
아라하바키가 아직 돌아가고 있는 거 맞아?
It's no wonder we couldn't get in touch with Haruka.
어쩐지 하루카와 연락이 안 되더라니
I hope she's all right.
괜찮길 바래야지
Was that just a dream?
그건... 꿈인가?
What's wrong?
뭐?
Is this is the research facility of my family?
이거... 우리 집 연구시설이잖아
Do you mean Spring Pharmaceuticals?
스프링 제약 말하는 거야?
Yes. But as I remembered, we had no research facility in Suoh.
응, 하지만 스오에 연구시설이 없는 것으로 알고 있어
Is this place really the Suoh we know?
여기 진짜 스오 맞아?
Something is amiss.
뭔가 이상한데?
Is this some kind of drug?
세이란시 표기가 붙은
It bears the marking of Seiran.
약 아니야?
This looks very similar to that ampoule.
그 앰플과 많이 닮았어...
Why is it here?
이게 왜 이곳에도 있는 거지?
What?
뭐야?
Kasane!
카사네
Major General Karen!
카렌 연대장님
You're finally here.
드디어 온 건가?
Major General!
연대장님
Kasane...
카사네...
Yes.
오케이...
There's hope after all.
이제 됐어
Kasane...
카사네...
Just now...
방금 그거...
It was Major General Karen's power.
카렌 연대장님의 초뇌능력이야
It was a skill of SS class, Brain Eater.
SS 스킬이지, 브레인 이터라고
He can copy another person's power and use it as his own.
타인의 초뇌능력을 복제해 자기 것처럼 사용할 수 있어
But why would he copy Kasane's power?
왜 카사네 초뇌능력을 복제하는 거지?
He can already use psychokinesis.
연대장님은 이미 염력을 가졌잖아
Sorry, I lost him.
미안, 놓쳐버렸어
Let's go outside.
나가자
We must find out what happened to Suoh.
스오에 무슨 일이 일어난 건지 확인도 해야 하니까
Kasane, can you move?
카사네, 괜찮겠어?
Yes.
응
People with powers.
세계 종말이 다가와도
Even while facing the end of the world, you still chose to fight it.
초뇌능력자는 여전히 싸워야 하는 걸까...
Hey! Hold on!
저기, 잠깐만요
Wait!
잠깐
You must be...
너...
Yuito Sumeragi, am I right?
유이토 스메라기 맞지?
And you are Kasane.
넌 카사네...
Kasane Randall.
카사네 랜들
I knew it.
역시
Are you really Yuito Sumeragi?
너 진짜 카사네 랜들이야?
Is this really him?
맞나봐
Judging by the voice, you must be Kyoka Eden and Shiden Ritter.
이 목소리는 쿄카 에덴과 시덴 리터인가?
I think I know what happened here.
이제 알겠다
It's hard to believe as it is,
믿기지 않지만
but Yuito Sumeragi, you've lost your sight.
유이토 스메라기, 너 지금 앞을 못 보는 거지?
-I am... -Arashi Spring.
-난... -아라시 스프링
I recognize the voice.
네 목소리를 기억해
We were supposed to be in Suoh capital of the year 2020.
우리는 신력 2020년의 스오에 있어야 하는데
But this place doesn't seem like it.
여긴 아닌 것 같아
Indeed.
그래
This is Suoh of the year 2070.
여기는 2070년의 스오야
It's 2070? But how?
2070년? 어떻게...
We are in the future?
우리가 미래의 세계로 온 거야?
It's time.
시간이 다 된 것 같군
From what I heard, only people with the power to time travel
타임 점프 뇌능력을 가진 자만이
can stay in a different timeline.
다른 시공간의 세계에 머물 수 있다고 들었어
Time travel power?
타임 점프 뇌능력?
Those caught up in the turbulence
무고하게 끌려간 자들은
will be sent back to their original timeline.
일정한 시간 동안 본래의 시공간으로 보내져
But I...
하지만 난...
Your power isn't psychokinesis.
네 초뇌능력은 염력이 아니야
It's the power to manipulate gravity and dimension, making it seem like psychokinesis.
염력같이 보이지만 실은 중력 조작과 차원 조작 능력이야
Kasane.
카사네
You have the power to travel through time.
넌 타임 점프 초뇌능력을 가졌어
You are the wielder of Red Strings.
즉 "레드 스트링스"의 소유자이지
So it wasn't a dream.
꿈이 아니었어
Red Strings...
레드 스트링스…
Those scarlet strings were the power to travel through time.
그 붉은 실들이... 시간 점프의 힘이었어
Arahabaki told me you would come from the past.
아라하바키가 알려줬어, 네가 과거에서 이곳으로 올 거라고
Until just now, I was doubting its prediction.
난 여전히 반신반의하고 있어
What happened?
무슨 일이 일어난 거야?
After Karen joined hands with Seiran to launch a rebellion,
카렌이 세이란시와 연합해 반란을 일으킨 뒤
New Himuka wanted to defend its pride as a powerful nation.
뉴히무카가 국가 위신을 지키기 위해
They put a man named Yuito Sumeragi on a pedestal
나 유이토 스메라기를 나라의 영웅 제단에 올려보냈어
to distract the people's attention.
국민의 시선을 분산하기 위해서지
My father was assassinated.
아버지는 암살 당했고
"PRIME SUSPECT: KASANE RANDALL" Kasane, you became the prime suspect.
(용의자, 카사네 랜들 소위) 넌 용의자로 체포되었어
I killed the Chairman?
내가 스메라기 의장님을 죽였다고?
I didn't kill your father.
난 네 아버지를 살해한 적 없어
The conflict between Suoh and Seiran escalated.
그 뒤로 스오와 세이란의 대립이 점차 심각해졌어
While I was battling the Others,
난 괴이를 토벌하면서
I was also fighting against the power users from Seiran.
세이란의 초뇌능력자와 맞서 싸웠어
That guy's gained more influence without me noticing it.
그리고 저건 어느샌가 점점 더 커졌지
You and I created this thing
저건 너랑 내가 만들었던
that looks like a black hole.
블랙홀 같은...
It's the Kunad Gate.
쿠나도 게이트야
We created it together?
우리가 만들었다고?
Our powers
너와 내 초뇌능력은
share the same property of manipulating gravity.
같은 유형의 중력 조작이야
In other words, I have the ability to travel through time.
그러니까 나도 타임 점프 뇌능력을 가진...
I am also a wielder of Red Strings.
레드 스트링스를 소유한 자란 말이지
Our powers resonated
우리의 힘이 공감을 생성해
and gave birth to the Kunad Gate.
쿠나도 게이트를 만든 거야
But I can't travel through time on my own.
하지만 난 시간을 초월하는 능력이 없어
-That was... -The Kunad Gate is growing.
-저건... -쿠나도 게이트가 점점 커져서
It's slowly consuming the world.
세상을 삼키고 있는 거야
The whole world...
세상을 삼켜?
Normally, the Gate will appear after a successful time travel.
이치대로 하면 타임 점프할 때 문이 생기고
It should disappear right away.
곧바로 사라지게 돼
But because my power was resonating to it,
하지만 내 힘과 공감을 생성하기 때문에
the Gate remained.
문이 계속 멈춰있는 거지
Ever since then, every time I use my power,
그리고 내가 초뇌능력을 사용할 때마다
the Gate will alter the space around it.
저 문은 주위의 공간을 비틀면서
It consumes the world around it.
온 세상을 삼키게 돼
Is there no way to stop it?
막을 방법은 없는 거야?
My power is sustaining the Gate.
내 초뇌능력이 쿠나도 게이트를 유지하도록 만드니까
When I die, the Gate will be gone too.
내가 죽어야만 쿠나도 게이트도 사라질 거야
That is the only way to get rid of the Gate.
쿠나도 게이트를 없앨 수 있는 유일한 방법이야
But I didn't choose that path.
하지만 난 그 길을 선택하지 않았어
Those around me persuaded me that there were other ways.
주위에서도 분명 다른 방법이 있을 거라고 나를 설득했었어
But the more I searched,
하지만 살아남을 방법을 찾을수록
the more I realized my death was the only way.
내가 죽지 않으면 문이 사라지지 않을 거란걸 알게 됐어
The Gate is growing.
오히려 점점 더 커졌지
It's growing because I'm still alive.
내가... 죽지 않았으니까...
Kasane, please kill me.
카사네, 나를 죽여줘
I'm asking you for a favor. I need you to take my life.
제발 나를 죽여줘
This is absurd.
뭔 헛소리야?
It was 50 years ago.
50년 전으로 돌아가
Before the Kunad Gate has expanded,
쿠나도 게이트가 커지기 전에
you must eliminate the false hero
가짜 영웅
you know as Yuito Sumeragi.
유이토 스메라기를 없애버려
You can't be serious.
내가 어떻게 그래...
I'm not even sure if I could go back.
게다가 난 돌아가는 법도 몰라
I know a way.
난 알고 있어
The Red Strings can be triggered by emotional fluctuation.
레드 스트링스는 감정 기복에 따라 발동돼
It happens when the heart suffers great trauma
예를 들면 네 마음이 거대한 충격을 받아
or a belief wavers.
동요하고 있을 때 말이지
The government ordered Suoh to carry on with the experiment to turn people into Others.
스오는 정부의 명령에 따라 인류를 괴이로 변하는 연구를 진행해왔어
Back then, the Suoh forces tried to turn the Seiran Garrison soldiers into Others.
그때 스오군은 본래 세이란군을 향해 괴이화 되는 탄알을 사격하려 했었어
No!
안돼
My father was the person who ordered the experiment.
그 연구 프로젝트의 지휘자는 바로 내 아버지였어
Even after being sung as a hero,
내가... 영웅이 된 내가...
even after I had learned the truth, I didn't stop the experiment.
진실을 알면서도 그 연구를 지속되게 한 거야
You let them carry on with the experiment?
네가 연구를 지속되게 했다고?
They turned most of the people into Others.
많은 인류를 괴이로 변화시켰어
Just like what they did to Naomi...
나오미처럼 말이지...
The research on power
초뇌능력을 연구하는 건
was a search for immortality.
내가 죽지 않는 방법을 얻기 위해서였어
Yuito, what have you done?
유이토, 너 뭐 하는 거야?
Kasane, I'm sorry.
미안해, 카사네
I leave the rest to you.
나머지는 너한테 맡길게
Yuito!
유이토
Take my life!
날 죽여줘
Do it for the sake of this world!
세상을 구하기 위해
Do it for the future!
미래를 구하기 위해...
Am I back to my timeline?
원래의 시간으로 돌아온 건가?
Kasane?
카사네...
Haruka?
하루카?
Arashi told me what happened.
아라시가 알려줬어
They are all safe.
지금 다들 괜찮아
But Suoh capital is in total chaos because of the uprising.
하지만 반란때문에 스오가 난리 났어
If you can hear me, please regroup with us as soon as possible.
내 목소리가 들린다면 얼른 우리한테로 와
The rendezvous point is...
장소는...
Haruka? Haruka?
하루카...
An uprising at Suoh capital...
누군가 스오에서 반란을 일으킨다고
Yuito and the team are there.
유이토도 그곳에 있어...
When I die, the Gate will be gone too.
내가 죽어야만 쿠나도 게이트도 사라질 거야
They turned most of the people into Others.
많은 인류를 괴이로 변화시켰어
Just like what they did to Naomi...
나오미처럼 말이지...
Yuito...
유이토...
The future with Yuito in it
유이토가 있는 미래는
is no longer accessible because of my time travel.
내가 타임 점프한 이유로 다시 돌아갈 수 없어
Now that I'm back,
현재로 돌아온
I can create a new future.
지금 이 시점부터 다른 미래가 생성되고 있어
However, the Kunad Gate didn't disappear.
하지만 쿠나도 게이트는 여전히 존재해
At this rate, the whole world...
이러다간 온 세상이...
Blind citizens of New Himuka
무모한 뉴히무카 국민들
and the foolish people who chose to ignore the reality,
그리고 모르는 척 눈감은 어리석은 자들아
I am Karen Travers.
난 카렌 트래버스다
I've awakened after I opened my eyes
뉴히무카 정치 관리 방침을 부정하고
to the government's conduct.
각성했지
My comrades and I...
나와 내 동료들은
-Karen, what are you planning? -have joined hands with Seiran.
-카렌, 넌 대체... -뜻이 같은 세이란시와 동맹을 맺기로 한다
That was close.
위험하네
Some agile variants show up from time to time.
가끔씩 저렇게 민감한 녀석들이 나타난다니까
I should keep an eye out for them.
조심해야겠네
Kagero?
카게로?
A shelter for the officials.
관리원이 이용하는 피난처인데
That was horrible.
참혹하네...
The gate is wide open.
입구가 열려있어
Chairman Sumeragi.
스메라기 의장님
Chairman Sumeragi. Wake up!
의장님, 조금만 버티세요
The OSF...
토벌군의...
That was Togetsu...
저건... 토게츠의...
Save your strength. I'll get the medics here.
일단 구조대부터 불러올게요
No, it's too late.
아니... 이미... 늦었어
Leave me be, go to a shelter.
난 냅두고... 어서 피난해...
Chairman, I have a question for you.
의장님, 한 가지 묻고 싶은 것이 있는데요
Was the organization that turned Naomi Randall into an Other
나오미 랜들이 괴이로 변한게...
the New Himuka Government?
진짜 뉴히무카 정부의 짓인가요?
The Yuito from the future was right.
역시, 50년 뒤의 유이토 말이 맞았어
Because I'm still alive.
내가... 죽지 않았으니까...
Take my life!
날 죽여줘
Do it for the sake of this world!
세상을 구하기 위해
Do it for the future!
미래를 구하기 위해...
Kasane...
카사네...
Father...
아빠...
Kasane, what are you doing?
카사네, 너 뭐 하는 거야?
What have you done to my father?
우리 아빠한테 무슨 짓을 한 거야?
This knife... Did you...
이 칼... 설마 네가...
Yuito!
유이토
Kasane?
카사네
Sir!
아저씨
It's best to retreat right now.
이럴 때는 철수하는 게 낫겠지?
Stop!
거기 서
Yuito...
유이... 토...
-Yuito... -Father!
-유이토 -아빠
Yuito, I'm sorry.
유이토, 미안하다...
I have something to tell you...
너한테... 해줄... 말이 있어...
Beware of this country...
조심해... 이 나라는...
They want you...
너를...
Father! This can't be real!
아빠, 거짓말이죠?
Father!
아빠
Father...
아빠...
It was a close call with all those people around.
쪽수가 많아서 위험하다니까
Kagero...
카게로
Why were you fighting Yuito?
왜 유이토와 싸운 거야?
Are you on Karen's side?
너 혹시 카렌과 한패야?
Was that why you killed Chairman Sumeragi?
그래서 스메라기 의장님을 살해한 건가?
No. It wasn't me.
아니야, 내가 죽인 거 아니야
I could ask you the same thing. Why were you there?
너야말로 그곳에 뭐하러 갔어?
I was going to rescue the council members.
난 평의회 사람들을 구하러 갔어
But sadly, I was too late.
아쉽게도 늦었지만 말이지
Kasane, sorry for breaking off just now.
카사네, 아까 연락 끊겨서 미안
I've regrouped with everyone.
나 지금 모두와 만났어
Our current location is...
지금 우리 위치가...
Kasane.
카사네
Kyoka.
쿄카
I'm glad you came back.
돌아와 줘서 다행이야
We were already back in this world before we even noticed it.
우리가 발견했을 때는 이미 현재로 돌아와 있었어
What are you talking about?
무슨 말들을 하는 거야?
We'll explain it another time, Kagero.
나중에 설명해줄게, 카게로
But what happened afterward, Kasane?
카사네, 그 뒤로 무슨 일이 있었던 건지
Please tell us.
말해줄래?
Red Strings and Kunad Gate?
레드 스트링스와 쿠나도 게이트라
Humans were turned into Others? And Naomi too?
인류가 괴이로 변한 것도, 나오미도
We have to kill Yuito to save the world?
유이토를 죽여야만 세상을 구할 수 있다니
This is beyond ridiculous.
그런 말을 누가 믿어?
That's what the future Yuito told me.
50년 뒤의 유이토 말에 따르면
Chairman Sumeragi was assassinated.
스메라기 의장님이 누군가에 의해 살해되었으니
Judging by the situation,
지금 상황으로 봐서는
I will become their prime suspect.
내가 용의자로 확정되겠네
Are we really going to take out
우리가 진짜...
that privileged kid?
그 도련님을 죽여야 하는 거야?
Kasane!
카사네
Karen!
카렌
It took long enough to find you, Kasane.
드디어 찾았다, 카사네
Report.
보고드립니다
The repair of Arahabaki is complete.
아라하바키의 복구 작업이 완료되었고
The rebels have retreated.
반란군의 포위망도 자진 철수했습니다
I see.
그래?
What about Kasane Randall?
카사네 랜들은?
We don't know where she is now.
아직 찾지 못했습니다
-Keep searching for her. -Understood.
-계속해서 수색해 -예
Kasane! What are you doing?
카사네, 너 뭐 하는 거야?
This knife... Did you...
이 칼... 설마 네가...
Personality rehabilitation
인격 교정은
is a widely known secret of the OSF.
이미 토벌군에서 다들 알고 있는 비밀이야
The stories are true.
그 말이 진짜였어...
All the people
모든 인류는
were born to be the government and the country's cattle!
국가를 위해, 정부를 위해 살아가고 또 이용당하는 가축인 셈이다
My father and brother knew...
아빠와 형은 모두 알고 있었어...
Beware of this country...
조심해... 이 나라는...
They want you...
너를...
Yuito?
유이토
It's all right. I'm fine.
괜찮아, 걱정 마
Where is Kasane?
카사네는?
We lost her.
놓쳤어
Thanks to Tsugumi's clairvoyance,
츠구미 투시 능력 덕분에
we've found Kyoka Platoon's rendezvous point.
쿄카 소대의 집합 장소를 알아냈어
Brother!
오빠
Kagero is with them too.
카게로도 거기에 있었어
Kagero?
카게로?
Around half of the OSF members
괴이 토벌군의 반은
have sided with Major General Karen and joined hands with the Seiran Garrison.
카렌 연대장과 함께 세이란군에 합류했어
There are rumors Seiran will declare its independence.
세이란이 독립선언을 할 거라는 소문도 들었어
Everyone.
자자
Wataru.
와타루
Psynet is back online.
사이넷이 복구됐어
Wataru, Haruka is...
와타루, 하루카가...
I know that already.
나도 알고 있어
She's left as well.
같이 간 거 맞지?
She is always worried about everything.
참 싱거운 녀석이라니까
It's normal she's worried about Kasane and the team.
카사네와 애들이 걱정됐나 봐
Well, don't be concerned.
뭐, 너무 걱정 말고
Yuito.
유이토
Brother.
형
Return to the headquarters at once.
당장 본부로 와
We need you to be the hero.
넌 반드시... 영웅으로 되어야 해
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
운명의 지시 따윈 필요 없어
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
분명 고쳐질 거라 믿으니까
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
앞으로도 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 말이야
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
눈부시게 빛나는 태양이 막을 내리고
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
세상의 끝에서 뭘 기다리고 있는걸까
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
♫Who can shake us♫
누가 우리를 위협해
♫Who can define us♫
누가 우리 대신 결정해
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
이건 우리만의 스토리야
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
네 마음속 미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
TRACKING DOWN NAGI
(추적, 나기)